

# **Tran Phuoc Anh Minh**

### PROFILE

•

 $\overline{\phantom{a}}$ 

March-07-1997

• Đà Nẵng, Việt Nam

#### SKILLS

#### 1. Web Developer:

- · HTML, CSS, Javascript
- · Boostrap, Antd
- ReactJS, TypeScript
- NodeJS, (ExpressJS, NestJS)
- Restful API, MySQL
- Cloud: Cloudinary
- ORM: TypeORM, Sequelize
- Hosting: DirectAdmin, Cpanel
- · Version Control: GIT

# 2. Search Engine Optimaztion:

- SEO Planning: Content, Offpage
- Audit Technical, Onpage
- Keyword Research
- Link Building
- Tracking User
- Tool: Google Analytic, Search Console, Tag Manager, Keyword Planner, Yandex Metrica
- · Wordpress, Plugin

## **INTERESTS**

Working

#### OVERVIEW

I am a dedicated individual with a strong work ethic, capable of dedicating over 8 hours per day to my job. Furthermore, I am diligent, friendly, and ambitious. I have cultivated a mature and responsible approach to every project I undertake. I make an effort to practice empathy in order to gain a deeper understanding of others' experiences and perspectives.

In a professional environment, I tend to be reserved and meticulously monitor my assigned responsibilities. I am constantly engaged in active learning, continuously exploring new methods to improve my work. I maintain a flexible mindset and enjoy synthesizing my acquired knowledge to generate innovative solutions that contribute to my projects. I prefer to propose multiple options and conduct testing to evaluate their effectiveness.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE** -

#### **INTERATE CORP**

11/2021 - 05/2023

**Position: SEO LEADER** 

- Implemented 4 projects Affiliate Global SEO: Finance, health, product reviews, promotions.
- Tasks implemented:
- + SEO Planning: Onpage, Offpage, Content
- + Keyword Research
- + Team management
- + Audit Content, Technical, Offpage
- + Building Website (Wordpress)
- + Manage hosting & domains

## **4LIFE ENGLISH CENTER**

03/2021 - 10/2021

#### Position: SEO LEADER (Freelancer)

- Tasks implemented:
- + SEO Planning: Onpage, Offpage, Content
- + Keyword Research
- + Team management
- + Audit Content, Technical, Offpage
- + Building Website (Wordpress)
- + Training team

## **DHV TEAM**

09/2020 - 10/2021

#### **Position: SEO Executive**

- Ecommerce Website (Global SEO Print On Demand Products)
- Tasks implemented:
- + SEO Planning: Onpage, Offpage, Content
- + Keyword Research
- + Team management
- + Audit Content, Technical, Offpage
- + Link building

- Helping the other people
- Research Information and Problem
- Seeking for anything new about technology, software, useful program serving for work
- Reading newspaper

CONANDO

### Position: SEO Intern, SEO Executive & SEO Leader

- Implemented many projects: Furniture, real estate, tourism...
- Tasks implemented:
- + SEO Planning: Onpage, Offpage, Content
- + Keyword Research
- + Team management
- + Audit Content, Technical, Offpage
- + Building Website (Wordpress)
- + Link building
- + Manage hosting & domains

## **EDUCATION** -

#### **RIKKEI ACADEMY**

05/2023 - Now

01/2019 - 09/2020

#### **Full Stack Javascript**

- Front-End: HTML, CSS, Javascript, ReactJS
- Back-End: NodeJS, ExpressJS, NestJS, MySQL, TypeORM, Restful API

#### **DUY TAN UNIVERSITY**

2015 - 2019

#### **Bachelor Of Business Administration**

· Business Administration (PSU) at Faculty of International

## **CERTIFICATIONS** -

- TOEIC: 695
- · IT Passport Certificate Japan
- · PSU scholarship (2017) with GPA 3.9/4.0

#### PROJECTS -

## **PROJECT 1: PETSHOP (ECOMMERCE SITE)**

- Front-End: HTML, CSS, Javascript, Boostrap
- Back-End: Javascript, Local Storage
- Features: CRUD, Add To Cart, Checkout, Manage Orders, Cancel Order
- Link Vercel:

## PROJECT 2: PETSHOP (ECOMMERCE SITE)

- Front-End: HTML, CSS, Javascript, Boostrap, Antd, ReactJS, TypeScript
- Back-End: Javascript, Local Storage, JSON Server
- Features: CRUD, Add To Cart, Checkout, Manage Orders/Bookings, Cancel Order, Comment, Booking, Coupons
- Link Git:

### PROJECT 3: PETSHOP (ECOMMERCE SITE)

- Front-End: HTML, CSS, Javascript, Boostrap, Antd, ReactJS, TypeScript
- Back-End: Local Storage, NodeJS, ExpressJS, Restful API, Sequelize
- Features: CRUD, Add To Cart, Checkout, Manage Orders/Bookings, Cancel Order, Comment, Booking, Coupons
- Link Git:

# PROJECT 4: PETSHOP (ECOMMERCE SITE)

- Front-End: HTML, CSS, Javascript, Boostrap, Antd, ReactJS, TypeScript
- Back-End: NestJS, Restful API, TypeORM
- Features: CRU, Add To Cart, Checkout with Paypal, Manage Orders/Bookings, Cancel Order, Comment, Booking, Coupons, Reset Password, Login With Gmail, Import Products by CSV, Export Products to CSV

• Link Git: